Toggle navigation [](https://spacedock.info/)

### Advanced search:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| `"term in quotes"` | For terms with spaces |
| `-term` | Exclude mods matching `term`, which can be a word or another advanced term |
| `user:[author]` | For mods by \[author\] |
| `ver:[version]` | For mods compatible with \[version\], can be either the full version number or a partial prefix, e.g. `ver:1.12` matches 1.12.0, 1.12.1, and 1.12.2 |
| `game:[game]` | For mods for \[game\], by number or part of name |
| `notif:[notification]` | For mods enabled for a given notification by part of name, e.g. `notif:CKAN` |
| `downloads:>[count]` | For mods with at least \[count\] downloads |
| `downloads:<[count]` | For mods with fewer than \[count\] downloads |
| `followers:>[count]` | For mods with at least \[count\] followers |
| `followers:<[count]` | For mods with fewer than \[count\] followers |

× **Done!** You'll get emailed updates for this mod.

×

This is meant to be easy to understand, but please [send us an email](mailto:support@spacedock.info) if you have any questions.

Terms of Use
============

We can and will ban you from the site if you fail to follow these terms. We may also take legal action against more serious violations.

The general idea is "be responsible". Follow these basic rules:

* Do not upload illegal content to the site
* Do not abuse or harrass other users
* Do not upload content you cannot grant licenses to
* Uploaders offer SpaceDock a royalty-free, worldwide license to distribute their mods upon uploading them

We can remove any content whenever we feel like it for any reason at all, with or without notifying the content owner.

Users of the site agree to monitor the site for changes, while the team makes a best-effort promise to notify about changes.

Legal Disclosure
================

Information in accordance with section 5 TMG  
  
Schlegel, Christian  
Hauptstr. 38d  
53604 Bad Honnef  

Contact
-------

Telephone: +49 175/8281852  
E-Mail: [support@spacedock.info](mailto:support@spacedock.info)  
Internetadresse: [http//spacedock.info](http://spacedock.info/)  

Person responsible for content in accordance with 55 Abs. 2 RStV
----------------------------------------------------------------

Schlegel, Christian  
Hauptstr. 38d  
53604 Bad Honnef  

Contact
-------

Telephone: +49 175/8281852  
E-Mail: [support@spacedock.info](mailto:support@spacedock.info)  

Indication of source for images and graphics
--------------------------------------------

some image source  

Disclaimer
----------

Accountability for content  
The contents of our pages have been created with the utmost care. However, we cannot guarantee the contents' accuracy, completeness or topicality. According to statutory provisions, we are furthermore responsible for our own content on these web pages. In this context, please note that we are accordingly not obliged to monitor merely the transmitted or saved information of third parties, or investigate circumstances pointing to illegal activity. Our obligations to remove or block the use of information under generally applicable laws remain unaffected by this as per §§ 8 to 10 of the Telemedia Act (TMG).  
  
Accountability for links  
Responsibility for the content of external links (to web pages of third parties) lies solely with the operators of the linked pages. No violations were evident to us at the time of linking. Should any legal infringement become known to us, we will remove the respective link immediately.  
  
Copyright  
Our web pages and their contents are subject to German copyright law. Unless expressly permitted by law (§ 44a et seq. of the copyright law), every form of utilizing, reproducing or processing works subject to copyright protection on our web pages requires the prior consent of the respective owner of the rights. Individual reproductions of a work are allowed only for private use, so must not serve either directly or indirectly for earnings. Unauthorized utilization of copyrighted works is punishable (§ 106 of the copyright law).  

Privacy Statement
=================

General
-------

Your personal data (e.g. title, name, house address, e-mail address, phone number, bank details, credit card number) are processed by us only in accordance with the provisions of German data privacy laws. The following provisions describe the type, scope and purpose of collecting, processing and utilizing personal data. This data privacy policy applies only to our web pages. If links on our pages route you to other pages, please inquire there about how your data are handled in such cases.  

Inventory data
--------------

(1) Your personal data, insofar as these are necessary for this contractual relationship (inventory data) in terms of its establishment, organization of content and modifications, are used exclusively for fulfilling the contract. For goods to be delivered, for instance, your name and address must be relayed to the supplier of the goods.  
(2) Without your explicit consent or a legal basis, your personal data are not passed on to third parties outside the scope of fulfilling this contract. After completion of the contract, your data are blocked against further use. After expiry of deadlines as per tax-related and commercial regulations, these data are deleted unless you have expressly consented to their further use.  

Social plug-ins from Facebook
-----------------------------

We use social plug-ins from facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plug-ins can be recognized by way of the Facebook logo or the supplement "Facebook Social Plug-in". For example, if you click on the "Like" button or leave a comment, the relevant information is transmitted directly from your browser to Facebook and stored there. Furthermore, Facebook makes your likes public for your Facebook friends. If you are logged into Facebook, it can assign the invocation of our page directly to your Facebook account. Even if you are not logged in or don't have a Facebook account, your browser sends information (e.g. which web pages you have called up, your IP address) which is then stored by Facebook. For details about handling of your personal data by Facebook and your related rights, please refer to the data privacy policy of Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php). If you do not want Facebook to map data collected about you via our Web sites to your Facebook account, you must log out of Facebook before you visit our web pages.  

Social plug-ins from Twitter
----------------------------

With Twitter and its Retweet functions, we use social plug-ins from Twitter.com, operated by Twitter Inc. 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107. If you use Retweet, the websites visited by you are announced to third parties and associated with your Twitter account. Details about handling of your data by Twitter as well as your rights and setting options for protecting your personal information can be found in Twitter's data privacy policy: [http://twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy)  

Newsletter
----------

Following subscription to the newsletter, your e-mail address is used for our own advertising purposes until you cancel the newsletter again. Cancellation is possible at any time. The following consent has been expressly granted by you separately, or possibly in the course of an ordering process:  
By clicking the "Recieve Updates" Button  
You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. If you no longer want to receive the newsletter, then unsubscribe as follows:  
By disableing updates for the respective mods  

Disclosure
----------

According to the Federal Data Protection Act, you have a right to free-of-charge information about your stored data, and possibly entitlement to correction, blocking or deletion of such data. Inquiries can be directed to the following e-mail addresses: ( [support@spacedock.info](mailto:support@spacedock.info) )

* * *

×

#### Login

 Remember Me

Close
